<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Two Activities</string>
    <string name="button_main">SEND</string>
    <string name="activity2_name">Second Activity</string>
    <string name="text_header">Message Received</string>
    <string name="editText_main">Enter Your Message Here</string>
    <string name="button_second">Reply</string>
    <string name="editText_second">Enter Your Reply Here</string>
    <string name="text_header_reply">Reply Received</string>
    <string name="button_label_toast">Toast</string>
    <string name="button_label_count">Count</string>
    <string name="count_initial_value">0</string>
    <string name="toast_message">Hello Toast</string>
    <string name="article_title">Today\'s Top News</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle1"><b>Chief Minister <i>Channi\'s</i> Hint For Congress After <i>Navjot Sidhu\'s</i> Warning</b></string>
    <string name="article_text1"><b>Congress: </b>The Congress may have kept any decision on a Chief Minister candidate in Punjab at bay ahead of elections but its two top faces, Chief Minister Charanjit Singh Channi and state Congress chief Navjot Singh Sidhu are not having it. https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/chief-minister-channis-hint-for-congress-after-navjot-sidhus-warning-2703096
\n\n
        As <b><i>Navjot Sidhu</i></b> said yesterday that "the people of Punjab" will pick the new Chief Minister, as opposed to the party high command, <b><i>Mr Channi</i></b> dropped a big hint of his own.
\n\n
<b>Highlights include:</b>
\n\n
The Congress should announce a chief minister candidate before the election, Mr Channi told a local channel, Pro Punjab TV. "Whenever the party has not announced a Chief Minister candidate, it has lost," he said when asked whether his party should name a candidate before the February 14 election. \n\n

        "When the party declared its CM candidate during the 2017 elections, it won. Before that, when it did not declare the candidate, it lost. Whenever the party has not announced the CM candidate, it has lost. So the party should announce it," he said.


\n\n
 <b><i>Mr. Channi</i></b> refused to comment on who should be named by the party but he talked about people waving at him wherever he went and even breaking through barricades to try and meet him.

\n\n
The comments by its two main leaders in Punjab presage trouble ahead for the Congress, which has been battling infighting while facing a tough challenge from <b>Aam Aadmi Party</b> (<b><i>AAP</i></b>), the <b><i>BJP-Amarinder Singh</i></b> alliance and the <b><i>Akali Dal-BSP </i></b>combine.

\n\n
While <b><i>Mr Channi</i></b> cautiously said the leadership will decide, Mr Sidhu was less subtle yesterday when he asked reporters: "Who told you the high command will pick the Chief Minister?"

\n\n
<b><i>Mr Sidhu</i></b> had been asked about Congress leader Sunil Zakhar \'s recent comment that the Congress would not announce a chief ministerial face before the election.
        \n\n
        The party will contest the polls under a "joint leadership", <b><i>Mr Jakhar</i></b> had said last month.

        "Everyone wants to be CM (Chief Minister). People of Punjab will decide who will be the Chief Minister. Who told you that the (Congress) high command will make the CM?" <b><i>Navjot Singh Sidhu</i></b>, state Congress chief, asked as a counter-question.
        \n\n
        "Do not have a false implication in your mind. People of Punjab will choose MLAs and they alone will decide who will be the Chief Minister," <b><i>Mr Sidhu</i></b> stressed.


</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle2"><b>Behind That Locked Door: Beatles Rarities!</b></string>
    <string name="article_text2">In a vault deep inside Abbey Road Studios in London — protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police-alarmed door — are something like 400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album. The best of the best were released by Apple Records in the form of the 3-volume Anthology series.
        For more information, see the Beatles Time Capsule at www.rockument.com.
\n\n
This volume starts with the first new Beatle song, “Free as a Bird” (based on a John Lennon demo, found only on <i>The Lost Lennon Tapes Vol. 28</i>, and covers the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live recordings from early concerts and BBC Radio sessions.
\n\n
<b>Highlights include:</b>
\n\n
<b><i>Cry for a Shadow</i></b> - Many a Beatle fanatic started down the outtake road, like I did, with a first listen to this song. Originally titled “Beatle Bop” and recorded in a single session that yielded four songs (the other three featured Tony Sheridan with the Beatles as a backing band), “Cry for a Shadow” is an instrumental written by Lennon and Harrison, which makes it unique to this day. John Lennon plays rhythm guitar, George Harrison plays lead guitar, Paul McCartney plays bass, and Pete Best plays drums. The sessions were produced by Bert Kaempfert in Hamburg, Germany, during the Beatles’ second visit from April through July of 1961 to play in the Reeperbahn-section clubs.
\n\n
<b><i>My Bonnie</i></b> and <b><i>Ain’t She Sweet</i></b> — At the same session, the Beatles played on “My Bonnie” (the first-ever single with Beatles playing), as the backing band for English singer Tony Sheridan, originally a member of the Jets. The popularity of this single in Liverpool brought the Beatles to the attention of Brian Epstein, who worked in the NEMS record store and tried to meet demand for the disc. John Lennon then sings a fine “Ain’t She Sweet” (his first-ever released vocal).
\n\n
<b><i>Searchin</i></b> — A Jerry Leiber - Mike Stoller comedy song that was a hit for the Coasters in 1957, and a popular live favorite of the Beatles. The Coasters also had a hit with “Besame Mucho” and the Beatles covered that song as well. Ringo Starr had by now replaced Pete Best on drums. The high falsetto is George, who also plays a hesitant lead guitar. This is from their first audition for Decca Records in London on Jan 1., 1962, live in the studio. The Grateful Dead would later cover “Searchin” with a similar arrangement, Pigpen doing the Paul vocals. A live version is available on outtake records featuring the Dead joined by the Beach Boys!
\n\n
<b><i>Love Me Do</i></b> — An early version of the song, played a bit slower and with more of a blues feeling, and a cool bossa-nova beat in middle. Paul had to sing while John played harmonica — a first for the group. Pete Best played drums on this version.
\n\n
<b><i>She Loves You – Till There Was You – Twist and Shout</i></b> — Live at the Princess Wales Theatre by Leicester Square in London, attended by the Queen. “Till There Was You” (by Meredith Wilson) is from the musical The Music Man and a hit for Peggy Lee in 1961. Before playing it, Paul said it was recorded by his favorite American group, “Sophie Tucker” (which got some laughs). At the end, John tells the people in the cheaper seats to clap their hands, and the rest to “rattle your jewelry” and then announces “Twist and Shout” (a song by Bert Russell and Phil Medley that was first recorded in 1962 by the Isley Brothers). A film of the performance shows the Queen smiling at John’s remark.
\n\n
<b><i>Leave My Kitten Alone</i></b> — One of the lost Beatle songs recorded during the “Beatles For Sale” sessions but never released. This song, written by Little Willie John, Titus Turner, and James McDougal, was a 1959 R&amp;B hit for Little Willie John and covered by Johnny Preston before the Beatles tried it and shelved it. A reference to a “big fat bulldog” may have influenced John’s “Hey Bulldog” (Yellow Submarine album), which is a similar rocker.
\n\n
<b><i>One After 909</i></b> — A song recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album was actually worked on way back in the beginning, six years earlier. This take shows how they did it much more slowly, with an R&amp;B feel to it.
</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle3"><b>Flight operations delayed at  Bhubaneswar airport due to dense fog</b></string>
    <string name="article_text3">IFlight operations were delayed at Biju Patnaik International Airport (BPIA) in Bhubaneswar on Friday morning because of poor visibility due to dense fog conditions.
\n\n
BPIA officials said the IndiGo flight en route from New Delhi to Bhubaneswar was diverted to Raipur due to poor visibility. The visibility was 150 metres at 9 am and 500 metres half an hour later.\n\n
<b>Highlights include:</b>
\n\n
<b><i>"First flight from Kolkata to Bhubaneswar landed at 9.27 am after the visibility improved. As instrument landing system is already installed in the airport, pilots can land the planes when the visibility is up to 800 metres as against the normal visibility of 1.5 km,"</i></b> - BPIA Director Pravat Ranjan Beuria told TNIE.
\n\n
        However, pilots of small aircraft, on their own discretion, can land even if the visibility is less than 800 metre.
\n\n
        <b>According to the India Meteorological Department (IMD), very dense fog condition is when the visibility is below 50 metres and during dense fog when the visibility is between 50 metres and 200 metres.</b>
\n\n
        <b><i>"On Friday morning, dense fog prevailed in the capital and very dense fog occurred in Angul. The fog condition is prevailing due to clear sky conditions, calm winds and moisture availability,"</i> said Bhubaneswar Meteorological Centre Scientist, Umasankar Das.</b>
\n\n

</string>
</resources>